<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources name="en" flag="gb" title="English">
	<string name="_bx_smtp"><![CDATA[SMTP Mailer]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_tester"><![CDATA[SMTP Mailer Tester]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_recipient"><![CDATA[Recipient]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_subject"><![CDATA[Subject]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_body"><![CDATA[Body]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_is_html"><![CDATA[Is HTML?]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_send_ok"><![CDATA[Mail has been successfully sent]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_send_fail"><![CDATA[Mail send failed]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_help"><![CDATA[Help]]></string>
	<string name="_bx_smtp_help_text"><![CDATA[
        <b>SMTP authentication </b> - most SMTP servers requires SMTP authentication, most probably you need to enable it.
        <br />
        <b>SMTP server name</b> - is it better to send mail from your site SMTP server, so it is probably the name of your site or localhost.
        <br />
        <b>SMTP username/SMTP password</b> - registered email account username and password, it is better to create different account for this purpose, like no-reply@mysite.com.
        <br />
        <b>From name of the message</b> - recipients will see this name as email sender, so it is probably your site name.
        <br />
        <b>Attach every outgoing email all files from kmailer/attach folder</b> - you can upload any files to <b>modules/boonex/smtpmailer/data/attach</b> folder on your site and enable this option setting to attach uploaded files to every email.
        <br />
        <b>Is your SMTP server requires secure connection</b> - you can disable it if your hostname is localhost, secure connection is not needed if you send mails from localhost.
        <br />
        <b>Enable SMTP mailer</b> - it is possible to disable SMTP mailer at all, for example if you have temporary problems with your SMTP server. 
        <br />
        <b>Override default sender email address</b> - set this the same as <b>SMTP username</b> email address, to avoid problems with mail marked as spam.
        <br />
        <br />
        Alternatively, you can get above options from your desktop mail client, if you are going to use the same email address for sending mail from your site.
        
        <hr class="bx-def-hr" />

        If emails still go to spam folder, check the following:
        <ul>
            <li>Try to set "Override default sender email address" field the same as "SMTP username" email address</li>
            <li>Make sure that "Override default sender email address" is valid and exists</li>
            <li>Try to change default email templates, it maybe that standard ones can be in spam filters, since they are used on a lot of sites by default</li>
            <li>Ask your members to add your site email to their contacts - when email is in user's contact list it always goes to inbox</li>
            <li><a href="http://www.boonex.com/trac/dolphin/wiki/TutorialTweakingSpamFilters" target="_blank">This is great tutorial</a> on how to whitelist your server in many popular webmail services, including yahoo</li>
        </ul>
]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_adm_stg_cpt_type"><![CDATA[SMTP Mailer]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_adm_stg_cpt_category_general"><![CDATA[General]]></string>
    
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_on"><![CDATA[Enable SMTP mailer]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_auth"><![CDATA[SMTP authentication (Is your SMTP server requires username and password?)]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_username"><![CDATA[SMTP username (only if SMTP authentication is enabled)]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_password"><![CDATA[SMTP password (only if SMTP authentication is enabled)]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_host"><![CDATA[SMTP server name or IP address]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_port"><![CDATA[SMTP server port number (25 - default, 465 - for secure ssl connection, 587 - for secure tls connection)]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_secure"><![CDATA[Is your SMTP server requires secure connection]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_allow_selfsigned"><![CDATA[Allow self-signed certificates]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_from_name"><![CDATA['From' name of the message]]></string>
    <string name="_bx_smtp_option_from_email"><![CDATA[Override default sender email address]]></string>
</resources>

